A Guide to the Papers of Howard W. Smith, 1933-1966
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: Miscellaneous Legislation
  - Appropriations (Box 13)
  - Banking (Box 13)
  - Civil Service (Box 13)
    Speech: "Declaration of Constitutional Principles" Cong. Record March 13, 1956
  - District of Columbia matters (Box 13)
  - D.C. Bridge and Tunnel (Box 13)
  - District Committee (Box 14)
  - Jones Point Bridge (Box 14)
  - D.C. Workmen's Compensation Act (Box 14)
  - Doctor Draft Law (Box 14)
  - Echo Park Dam-and other similar projects (Box 15)
  - Aid to Education (Box 15)
  - Frying Pan-Arkansas Project 84th Congress (Box 15)
  - Jurisdiction of Federal Courts (Box 15)
  - Foreign Aid (Box 15)
  - H.R. 3769-(Forrester's Bill)-to restore the Administration of our educational facilitiies to the respective states (Box 15)
  - Federal Housing Bill (Box 16)
  - Public Housing (Box 16)
  - Immigration (Box 16)
  - Labor Legislation (Box 16)
  - Misc. Legislation (Box 17)
  - Misc. Legislation (Box 17)
    84th Congress - 2nd Session
  - Misc. Legislation (Box 18)
  - Military & Reserve Training (Box 18)
  - Postal Legislation (Box 18)
  - Patman Resolution to Investigate Federal Reserve Board (Box 18)
  - Reciprocal Trade Agreement (Box 18)
    83rd Congress
  - Rules Committee (Box 19)
  - Democratic Steering Committee (Box 19)
  - Social Security Legislation (Box 19)
  - Socialized Medicine (Box 19)
    82nd Congress
  - Salaries-Member of Congress and Judiciary (Box 19)
  - States Rights- Cong. Record, 84th Congress, Jan. 6, 1955 (Box 19)
  - Taxation of Co-Operatives (Box 19)
  - Tax Legislation (Box 19)
  - Handbook on TVA (Box 19)
  - TVA-Self-Financing (Box 19)
  - Veterans Legislation (Box 19)
  - Wage-Hour Act (Box 20)
  - Whip (Box 20)
  - Appropriations (Box 20)
    85th Congress
  - Agriculture (Box 20)
  - Banking (Box 21)
  - Housing (Box 21)
  - Civil Service Legislation (Box 21)
  - D.C. matters (Box 21)
  - H.R. 7396-Southeast Hospital (Box 22)
  - Joint Committee for Study of Washington Metropolitan Youth Programs (Box 22)
  - Study of Municipal Problems in Washington Area (Box 22)
  - H. Con. Res. 172-Study of Municipal Problems in the Washington Area (Box 22)
  - State of the Nations Capital (February, 1958) (Box 22)
  - District Committee (Box 22)
  - Davis Committee-D.C. Schools (Box 22)
  - Misc. Legislation (File No. 1) (Box 23)
  - Misc. Legislation (File No. 2) (Box 24)
  - Echo Park Dam-and similar projects (Box 24)
  - Remarks from Congr. Record-85th Congress (Box 24)
  - Aid to Education (Box 24)
  - Foreign Aid (Box 25)
  - Immigration (Box 25)
  - Labor Legislation (Box 25)
  - Misc. Legislation (File No. 2) (Box 25)
  - Natural Gas (Box 26)
  - Vepco-Locating Plant in Loundoun County (Box 26)
  - Pollution (Box 26)
  - Postal Legislation (Box 27)
  - Commerce Dept. Foreign Trade Impact Study-State of Va. 1958 (Box 27)
  - Railroad Legislation (Box 27)
  - Reciprocal Trade (Box 27)
  - Reicher, Frieda (Box 27)
  - Speech, Cong. Record, Jan 28, 1948, reprint re: States Rights (Box 27)
  - Rules Committee (Box 27)
  - Rules Committee (Box 28)
  - Social Security (Box 28)
  - Tax Legislation (Box 28)
  - Tax Legislation-printed reports (Box 29)
  - TVA Legislation (Box 29)
  - Unemployment Legislation "DOLE" 85th Congress-2nd Session (Box 29)
  - Veterans Legislation (Box 29)
  - Appropriations (Box 29)
    86th Congress
  - Agriculture (Box 30)
  - Banking (Box 30)
  - Civil Rights (Box 30)
  - Civil Rights-Northerners Side with Southerners on Issue (Box 30)
  - Civil Rights Bills (Box 31)
  - Civil Service Legislation (Box 31)
  - Confederate Widows Pension (Box 31)
    [85th-86th Congresses]
  - D.C. Matters (Box 31)
  - D.C. Committee, 1961-62 (Box 31)
  - D.C. Committee (Box 32)
  - [D.C.] Home Rule (Box 32)
  - Clippings (Box 32)
  - Social Security (Box 33)
  - Gasoline Tax (for financing highway program) (Box 33)
  - Tax Legislation (Box 33)
  - TVA Legislation (Box 33)
  - Veterans Legislation (Box 33)
  - Minimum Wage (Box 34)
  - Postal Legislation (Box 35)
  - Pollution (Box 35)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 35)
  - Panama (Box 35)
  - Rules Committee (Box 35)
  - Applicants for Rules Committee Position (Box 36)
  - Rules Committee (Box 36)
    86th Congress - 2nd Session
  - Rules Committee - Criticisms (Box 36)
  - Railroad Legislation (Box 36)
  - Reciprocal Trade Legislation (Box 36)
  - Labor Legislation (Box 37)
  - Labor Legislation (Box 37)
  - Labor Legislation - Steel and Railroad Strike 1959 (Box 38)
  - Steel Strike-1959 (Box 38)
  - H.R. 9070-amend National Labor Relations Act (Box 38)
  - Misc. Legislation (Box 38)
  - Misc. Legislation (Box 39)
  - NLRB (Box 40)
  - Congressional Record Remarks (Box 40)
  - Joint Committee Washington Metropolitan Problems (Box 40)
  - Education Legislation (Box 40)
  - Foreign Aid Legislation (Box 41)
  - Natural Gas Legislation (Box 41)
  - Housing Legislation (Box 41)
  - Housing Legislation (File No. 2) (Box 41)
  - Immigration Legislation (Box 42)
  - Labor Legslation (Box 42)
    86th Congress, 1959 (to be brought forward next year)
  - Correspondence with Mayor W.L. Howard (La.) re: Southwide Agriculture (Box 42)
    87th Congress
  - D.C. Matters (Box 43)
  - Military Construction (H.R. 5000) (Box 43)
  - Joint Committee on Washington Metropolitan Problems (Box 43)
  - Un-American Activities (Box 43)
  - Department of Urban Affairs (Box 43)
  - Unemployment Compensation (Box 43)
  - Veterans Legislation (Box 43)
  - Rules (Box 44)
    8th Congress
  - Rules Committee (Box 44)
  - Speakership and Majority Leader (Box 44)
  - White House Press Releases (Box 44)
  - White House Press Releases (Box 45)
  - White House (Box 45)
  - Minimum Wage Legislation (Box 45)
  - Misc. Legislation (Box 46)
  - "Is the Purpose Federal Aid to Education or Federal Control of Legislation?" [statement by Judge Smith-contents of folder really concern Federal Aid to Education] (Box 47)
  - Battle Act (Box 47)
  - Foreign Trade-Kitchin Res. House Res. 403 (Box 47)
  - Railroad Legislation (Box 47)
  - Reciprocal Trade - 1962 (Box 48)
  - Reciprocal Trade - 1962 (Box 48)
    87th Congress - 2nd Session
  - Rules Committee - Special (Box 48)
  - House Rules - Changes in 86th Congress (Box 48)
  - Rules Committee (Box 49)
  - Social Security (Box 49)
  - Social Security (Box 50)
  - Tax Legislation (Box 50)
  - Taxation on Mutuals (Box 50)
  - Foreign Aid (Box 51)
  - Federal Equal Opportunity Employment Act (Box 51)
  - Frying Pan-Arkansas (Box 51)
  - Highway Legislation (Box 51)
  - Housing (Box 51)
  - Labor (Box 51)
  - Misc. Legislation File No. 2 (Box 52)
    87th Congress-1st Session
  - Correspondence on Misc. Legislation (Box 52)
  - Peace Corps (Box 53)
  - Postal Rates - Increase H.R. 7927 (Box 53)
  - Agriculture - 2nd Session (Box 53)
  - Agriculture (Farm Bill - H.R. 11222) May 16, 1962 (Box 53)
  - Agriculture - 2nd Session (Box 53)
  - Appropriations (Box 54)
  - Banking (Box 54)
  - Civil Rights (Box 54)
  - Civil Service (Box 54)
  - Connally Amendment (Box 54)
  - U.S. Intelligence Investigation (Box 54)
  - Misc. D.C. Matters (Box 54)
  - District Committee (Box 54)
  - S. 722 - Area Redevelopment-(Depressed Areas) (Box 54)
  - School Aid Bills (Box 55)
  - Impacted Areas - Federal Aid to Education (Box 55)
  - Impacted Areas - Correspondence (Box 55)
  - Education (Box 55)
  - H.R. 132-Education Television (Report 999) (Box 56)
  - H.R. 8986 - Salary Bill - Government Employees Salary Reform Act of 1964 (Box 56)
  - H.R. 11377 - Economic Opportunity Act of 1964 (Box 56)
  - H.R. 12580 -Kerr-Mills Bill-Social Security Amendments (Box 56)
  - Misc. Legislation-Reciprocal Trade (Box 56)
    88th Congress
  - Misc. Legislation-Social Security (Box 56)
  - H.R. 9903-Transportation Bill (Box 56)
  - Un-American Activities (Box 57)
  - Mass Transportation (Box 57)
  - Veterans (Box 57)
  - Public Law 88-272 [H.R. 8363] - to amend Internal Revenue Code of 1954 (Box 57)
  - H.R. 10 - Voluntary Pension Plans for Self-Employed Individuals (Box 57)
  - H.R. 8363 - Revenue Act of 1964 (Box 57)
  - Misc. Legislation-Tax [Reduction-Correspondence re] Bill (Box 57)
  - Tax Reduction Bill (Box 58)
  - Misc. Legislation - Veterans (Box 58)
  - Presidential Messages, etc. (Box 58)
  - Coal Mine Safety Bill (Box 58)
  - Housing - Misc. Legislation (Box 58)
  - Immigration-Misc. Legislation (Box 58)
  - Junkets (Box 58)
    88th Congress - 1st Session
  - Labor - Misc. Legislation (Box 58)
  - Minimum Wage (Box 59)
  - Revenue Act of 1963 [H.R. 8363] (Box 59)
  - Medicare (Box 59)
  - Pollution (Box 59)
  - Postal - Misc. Legislation (Box 59)
  - Peace Corps - Youth Corps (Box 59)
  - Poll Tax - Abolishing (1962) (Box 59)
  - Poverty (Box 60)
    88th Congress - 2nd Session
  - Miscellaneous Legislation - [correspondence re] (Box 60)
  - Railroad Legislation (Box 61)
  - Rules Committee (Box 61)
  - Rules Committee (Box 62)
  - Civil Rights - Special (Box 62)
  - Civil Service Legislation (Box 62)
  - Cuba (Box 63)
    [86-88th] 87 Congress
  - Coal (Box 63)
    [87-88th Congress]
  - Civil Rights (Box 63)
  - Civil Rights (Box 64)
  - Civil Rights Papers - Used in Floor Debate (Box 64)
  - Civil Rights [Congressional bills] (Box 64)
  - Clippings - Civil Rights - Cong. Record - 88th Congress, 2nd Session, July 2, 1964 (Box 64)
  - Debt Limit (Box 64)
  - District Committee - Misc. Legislation (Box 64)
  - D.C. Matters - Misc. Legislation - Proposed D.C. Housing Order (Box 65)
  - Education - Misc. Legislation (Box 65)
  - Foreign Aid - Misc. Legislation (Box 65)
  - Miscellaneous Legislation - Agriculture (Box 65)
  - Misc. Legislation - Appropriations (Box 66)
  - Independent Offices and National Science Foundation - 88th Congress (Box 66)
  - Appropriations (Special) 88th Congress - 1st Session (Box 66)
  - Armed Services Appropriations (Box 66)
  - H.R. 10939 [88th Congress - 2nd Session] - Department of Defense Appropriations (Box 66)
  - Foreign Aid Appropriations (Box 66)
  - Public Works Appropriations (Box 66)
  - Appropriations (Box 66)
  - Appropriations - (Various) (Box 66)
  - Interior Appropriations (Box 66)
  - Appalachian Regional Development Act of 1964 (Box 66)
  - Area Redevelopment (Box 67)
  - Debt Ceiling (Box 67)
  - Public Works Bill on Sending it to Conference [Committee] (Box 67)
  - Beef Imports (Box 67)
  - Banking Legislation (Box 67)
  - Viet Nam [correponsdence, etc.] (Box 67)
  - Veterans Legislation (Box 68)
    89th Congress
  - Voting (Box 68)
  - Voting Rights (Box 68)
  - Analysis of H.R. 6400 - "Voting Rights" Bill (Box 68)
  - Mary Washington College (Box 68)
  - University of Virginia (Box 69)
  - Student Legal Forum Speech - Oct. 12, 1961 (Box 69)
  - "Meet the Press" - 26 Jan. 1964 - Civil Rights (Box 69)
  - Rules Committee (Box 70)
    89th Congress - 1st Session
  - Rules Committee (Box 71)
  - Rules Committee (Box 71)
    89th Congress - 2nd Session
  - Reapportionment - Federal 88th Congress - 1st Session (Box 72)
  - H.R. 11971 (to limit jurisdiction of Federal courts in reapportionment cases) (Box 72)
  - Railroad Legislation (Box 72)
  - Social Security (Box 72)
  - Sales Participation Act - Second Session (H.R. 14544 - 89th Congress) (Box 72)
  - Tax Legislation (Box 72)
  - Un-American Activities Committee (Box 73)
  - Urban Renewal (Box 73)
  - Misc. Correspondence [re: Legislation] (Box 73)
  - Miscellaneous Legislation (Box 74)
  - Medical Legislation (Box 74)
  - Medicare (Box 74)
  - Pollution (Box 74)
  - Postal Legislation (Box 74)
  - Poverty Legislation (Box 75)
  - Economic Opportunity (Box 75)
  - Firearms Legislation (Box 75)
  - Foreign Aid & Interdevelopment (Box 75)
  - FBI-Successor for J. Edgar Hoover (Box 75)
  - Habeas Corpus - H.R. 5958 (Box 75)
  - Supreme Court Decision [2 folders] (Box 76)
  - Supreme Court Apportionment Ruling - March 26, 1962 (Box 76)
  - Supreme Court of the U.S. - Opinions [Prayer Decision] Oct. Term, 1961 (Box 77)
  - Hearing on Limitations of Appealate Jurisdiction of the U.S. Supreme Court (Box 77)
  - Constitution - Personal File (Box 77)
  - Earl Warren [chiefly correspondence urging impeachment] (Box 77)
  - Civil Rights - Correspondence (Box 77)
  - Hearings before Rules Committee - to admit Hawaii and alaska to the Union (Box 77)
  - H.R. 10765 - Longshoreman's and Harbor Worker's Compensation Act (Box 77)
  - H.R. 627 - Civil Rights (Box 77)
  - H.R. 462-amending Rules to Create Standing Committee (Box 78)
  - H.R. 4441-Administrative Procedure and Practice - April, 1956 (Box 78)
  - H.R. 6496-to make the Commission on Civil Rights a Permanent Agency (Box 78)
  - H.R. 8446-The National Portrait Gallery Act (Box 78)
  - H.R. 2017 - City Income Tax Withholding from Compensation of Federal Employees (Box 78)
  - [Miscellaneous Legislation] (Box 78)
  - Meet the Press - 26 January 1964 (Box 78)
  - [Correspondence re appearance on "Meet the Press"] (Box 78)
  - Framed telegram, "If Our Country Had More Howard W. Smith's and Less Howard K. Smith's..." (Box 78)
  - Change in Committee Rules - Jan. 1961 (Box 79)
  - Change in Committee Rules - Packing (Box 79)
  - CBS - "Keeper of the Rules", Jan 19, 1961 (Box 80)
  - Misc. Correspondence re: Rules Committee Change - 87th Congress (Reflects public reaction to Proposal) 1961 (Box 80)
  - Correspondence after 1961 CBS Reports "Keeper of the Rules" Appearance (Box 81)
  - Correspondence after 1961 CBS Reports "Keeper of the Rules" Appearance (Box 82)
  - Congressional Record, 31 January 1961 "Save-Rules Fight" (Box 82)
  - Congressional Record, 9 January 1963 [Rules Committee consideration] (Box 82)
  - D.C. and Va. Boundary Line - Report of the Commission - H.D. #374 (Box 83)
    74th Congress
  - H.R. 9745-to guarantee collective bargaining re: U.S. or Agency thereof; "Died in Comm." Hearings thereon (Box 83)
    75th Congress
  - H.R. 262-to require reports of contributors and registration of lobby [bill introduced by Smith] (Box 83)
  - Congressional Record, 18 March 1940; pages marked (Box 83)
    76th Congress, 3rd Session
  - H.R. 6616-amendment to the Act of 1941 to expedite the prosecution of the war effort [bill introduced by Smith] (Box 83)
    77th Congress, 2nd Session
  - H.R. 6066-to dismiss the causes of labor disputes [bill introduced by Smith] (Box 83)
  - H.R. 4926-reports, Department of Labor, Fed. Security Agency - appropriation 1942 (Box 83)
  - H.R. 627 - Hearings, Civil Rights protection (Box 83)
  - H.R. 462-Hearings, to establish Committee on Administrative Practice (Box 83)
  - H.R. 258-Rerport to investigate NLRB [Smith notes] (Box 83)
  - National Labor Relations Act - Report of Comm. To investigate NLRB; submitted by Smith (Box 83)
    76th Congress
  - Conditions of Government Contracts - Hearings on S1032, H.R. 3331, H.R. 6395 (Smith notes) (Box 83)
  - NLR Act and proposed amendements - Hearings S1000, S1264, S1392, S1550, S1580, and S2123 (Box 83)
  - H.R. 102-Hearings, special committee to investigate Exec. Agencies (Smith, Chairman) (Box 83)
  - H.R. 102-Reports of Select Committee to investigate executive agencies; smith Report on same (Box 83)
  - Hearings - Special Committee on Executive agencies (Box 83)
  - H.R. 266-Hearings, Committee on Education and Labor, U.S. Senate (Box 83)
  - H.R. 88-Committee to Investigate Executive Agencies (Box 83)
  - Congressional Record (See Smith notes)
  - (Misc.) - Feb. 2, 1943 - June 26, 1945 (Box 84)
  - Subseries A-79th Congress:
    - H.R. 7003-to authorize the Sec. of War to permit the delivery of water from Washington aqueduct pumping system station to the Falls Church water supply system [bill introduced by Smith] (Box 84)
    - H. Joint R. 352-creating joint committee to study and recommend legislation concerning labor relations (Box 84)
    - H. Joint R. 280 -creating joint committee to study and recommend legislation concerning labor relations (Box 84)
    - H.R. 3937-to repeal the War Labor Disputes Act and to abolish the National War labor Board (Box 84)
    - H.R. 4789-to amend section 702 of title 34 of the United States Code (Box 84)
    - H.R. 4796-to amend section 905 of title 10 of the United States Code (Box 84)
    - H.R. 88-hearings before the Special Committee to investigate executive agencies. Parts 1-5 (Box 84)
    - H.R. 88-intermediate reports, No. 8, 9, 10, of the select committee (Box 84)
    - H.R. 310 and P.L. 118 (80th Congress) - to authorize the Sec. of War to permit the delivery of water from the D.C. and Arlington County water systems to the Falls Church or other water systems in the metropolitan area of the District of Columbia in Virginia. (See H.R. 7003 above) (Box 84)
    - Congressional Record - Jan. 23, 31, 1946 - 79th Congress (Box 84)
  - Subseries B-80th Congress, 1st session:
    - P.L. 101 - [H.R. 3020] - to amend N.L.R.B. (Box 84)
    - P.L. 108 - [H.R. 310] - to permit delivery of water to Falls Church (Box 84)
    - H.R. 310-report no. 378, authorizing Sec. of War to permit water delivery to Falls Church (Box 84)
    - Disc. 482-to authorize the Secretary of War to permit the delivery of water from D.C. and Arlington water systems to the Falls Church or other water systems in the metropolitan area of the District of Columbia. See H.R. 310 and P.L. 118 above. (Box 84)
    - H.R. 312-to amend section 702 of Title 34 of U.S. Code (Box 84)
    - H.R. 313-to amend section 905 of Title 10 of U.S. Code (Box 84)
    - P.L. 533 - H.R. 8578-authorizing loans from the United States Treasury for the expansion of the District of Columbia Water system. (81st Congress) (Box 84)
    - H.R. 310-hearings before the Sub-committee on Buildings and Grounds of the Committee of Public Works (Box 84)
  - Subseries C - 81st Congress-1st Session
    - H.R. 1432 - to amend the act approved June 29, 1948 entitled "Act to Authorize the Issuance of a Stamp Commerative of the Two-hundredth Anniversary of the Founding of the City of Alexandria, Virginia" (Box 84)
    - H.R. 1936-to authorize and direct the Secretary of the Interior to grant a right of way (Box 84)
    - H.R. 1937-to provide additional revenue for the District of Columbia (Box 84)
    - H.R. 2153-to authorize the issuance of a stamp commerative of the 200th anniversary of the founding of the county of Culpeper, Virginia (Box 84)
    - H.R. 2694-to amend the District of Columbia alcoholic Beverage Control Act (Box 84)
    - H.R. 2935-for the reflief of Mrs. Benjamin Betts. Passed as P.L. 39 (Box 84)
    - H.R. 3014-for the relief of Roger Stanford (Box 84)
    - H.R. 3297-to authorize the addition of certain lands to Manassas National Battlefield Park, Virginia and for other purposes (Box 84)
    - H.R. 3347 - to provide additional revenue for the District of Columbia (passed 1949) (Box 84)
    - H.R. 3704-to provide additional revenue for the District of Columbia - passed as P.L. 76 (Box 84)
    - H.R. 4108 - for the relief of Robert I. Cryster (Box 84)
    - H.R. 4108-for the relief of Ladislase Hudec, Gisella Hudec, Alessa Hudec, who entered the United States on June 25, 1948 at New York City (Box 84)
    - H.R. 4109-for the relife of Kenneth McKelvie (Box 84)
    - P.L. 426, H.R. 4502-to authorize the Secretary of the Army to dispose of a certain easement near Fort Belvoir (Box 84)
    - P.L. 698, H. R. 6104-to authorize the establishment of an educational agency for surplus property within the government of the District of Columbia (Box 84)
    - H.R. 8001-to amend the act entitled "An Act to Define the Real Property Exempt from Taxation in the District of Columbia" (Box 84)
  - Subseries D - 81st Congress-2nd Session
    - H. R. 8106-to amend the D.C. Teacher's Salary Act of 1947 (Box 84)
    - H.R. 8124-for relife of Arthur C. Thompson (Box 84)
    - H.R. 8372-to amend certain tax laws applicable to the District of Columbia (Box 84)
    - H.R. 8745-for the relief of Jindrich (Henri) Nosek and Mrs. Zdenka Nosek (Box 84)
    - H.R. 9383-to amend the Railroad Retirement Act of 1937 to permit certain employed persons to be paid annuities under such acts. (Box 84)
    - H.R. 9396-for the relief of Maurice Mumford (Box 84)
    - H. Joint R. 435 - providing for a commission to investigate strikes and other interruptions of work in industries essential to the national welfare (Box 84)
    - H. R. 455 -resolution that rule 13 be amended by adding thereto a new paragraph (Box 84)
    - H.R. 475-resolution that the Farewell Address of George Washington shall be read to the House on Feb. 22 (Box 84)
    - H.R. 476 - resolution recognizing the death of Schyler Otis Bland, Congressman from the State of Virginia (Box 84)
  - Subseries E -82nd Congress-1st Session
    - H.R. 1066-to fix the responsibilities of the dispersing officer and the auditor of the District of Columbia and for other purposes (Box 84)
    - H.R. 1068-to promote the extension of the parkway and playground system of the National Capital and northern Virginia environs of Washington (Box 84)
    - H.R. 2256-bill to amend Railroad Retirement Act of 1937 to permit certain employed persons to be paid annuities under such act (Box 84)
    - H.R. 2327-bill to authorize exchange of lands acquired by U.S. for Prince William Forest Park, Prince William County, Virginia, for consolidating Federal holdings therein (Box 84)
    - H.R. 2530-bill to amend certain tax laws applicable to District of Columbia (Box 84)
    - H.R. 2658-bill to amend Selective Service Act of 1948 (Box 84)
    - H.R. 2954-to authorize and direct the Commissioners of the District of Columbia to construct the bridge over the Potomac River in the vicinity of Shepherd's landing and for other purposes (Box 84)
    - H. R. ? Bill to provide for preparation of plans for growth of National Capital region and D.C. (Box 84)
    - H.R. 5235 - to authorize and direct the Commissioners of the District of Columbia to make such studies and investigations deemed necessary concerning the location and construction of a bridge over the Potomac River in the vicinity of Shepherd's Landing (Box 84)
    - H.R. 5256-to secure the attendance of witnesses from without the District of Columbia in criminal proceedings (Box 84)
  - Subseries F - 82nd Congress - 2nd Session
    - H.R. 2327 - to exchange lands in Prince William County (Box 84)
    - H.R. 7888 & S 913 hearings before the Committee on Rules - House of Representatives. To create a joint committee on the budget. (Box 84)
    - H. Con. R. 210 - introduced by Smith to oppose Executive Order of April 1952 by the President of the United States seizing various private properties (Box 84)
    - P. L. 592 - The National Capitol Planning Act of 1952. To amend the act of June 6, 1924 relating to the National Capitol Park and Planning Commission (Box 84)
    - H.R. 7502 - to amend the act of June 6, 1924 relating to the National Park and Planning Commission. Passed as P.L. 592 (Box 84)
    - H.R. 7888, S. 913 - hearings before Committee on Rules on a bill to amend Legislative Reorganization Act of 1946 to provide for more effective evaluation of fiscal requirements of executive agencies of U.S. government and to create a joint committee in the budget (Box 84)
  - Subseries G.-83rd Congress-1st Session
    - H.R. 3380 - to authorize the exchange of lands acquired by the United States for Prince William Forest Park, Prince William County, Virginia for the purpose of consolidating federal holdings therein and for other purposes (Box 84)
    - H.R. 4226-to regulate the operation and conduct of commercial parking of motor vehicles in the District of Columbia (Box 84)
    - H. Con. R. 28 - commerating the 300th Anniversary of the creation of Westmoreland County, Virginia (Box 84)
    - P.L. 144, H.R. 3380 - an act to authorize the exchange of land acquired by the United States for Prince William Forest Park, Prince William County, Virginia for the purpose of consolidating federal holdings therein (Box 84)